<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Thinks Too Much</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Thinks Too Much</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1. Hello World!</title>
      <link>/post/helloworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/helloworld/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my Site! This is my blog&amp;hellip; I guess.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to find a place to collect and share my ideas for years now. Hopefully this becomes a regular habit that I can maintain for years, but we need to start small by starting the site and introducing what I do.
Things to see I am an avid enjoyer of what I believe to be a stereotypical collection of hobbies: Hiking, History, Philosophy, Politics, Art, and Computers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024/11/25 50 Round Handgun Training Manual</title>
      <link>/post/50rdtrain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/50rdtrain/</guid>
      <description>Dry Fire Drills NOTE: All Drills should be performed using your Every Day Carry Clothes and Gear, The point is to be ready when an actual situation occurs.
Ideal Draws (10-15 minutes daily) Start from a loose, comfortable standing position. At random you will put your hands up like you’re surrendering then draw your firearm and point it straight at the mirror using your reflection as both a target and to study your form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024/11/26 So You&#39;re Buying a Gun</title>
      <link>/post/buyingagun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/buyingagun/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to firearms ownership! This document is to help you learn the basics and give you the fundamental skills necessary to defend yourself and your loved ones.
What to know Firearms are tools that are there to help you survive in either a deadly confrontation or a dire survival situation. They are not toys. You can certainly have fun with them, but there is a real gravity to being a firearms owner that should never be lost on you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024/12/02 Atheist Occultism</title>
      <link>/post/atheistoccult/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/atheistoccult/</guid>
      <description>There is an obvious contradiction in being both an Atheist and an Occultist. How can I believe and practice Magick and Religious rituals if I do not believe in the powers that I am acting as if I am controlling? What gives me the right to disrespect these practices and traditions? Simple, it’s fun and I do not worry about gods or demons smiting me.
That is of course the short version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024/12/08 Selfishness and Why I got Snipped</title>
      <link>/post/selfishsnips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/selfishsnips/</guid>
      <description>Intro December 6th 2024, I received a vasectomy at the age of 27. I have spent the weekend healing and going over in my head everything I want to tell people about why I did it and what lead me to finally do it. I’ve been listening to podcasts about it and reading stories on Reddit, and I have some thoughts on why I specifically want to get it done. Primarily I wanted to focus on my ideas of selfishness and how it helps us go navigate the human experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024/12/15 Dating apps and Mental Health</title>
      <link>/post/datingapps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/datingapps/</guid>
      <description>Recently I read a blog post from a friend of mine and his thoughts on dating. It was a good read and I&amp;rsquo;ll need to ask if he is okay with me sharing it here. However, he had a whole set of reasons to hate dating apps saying they&amp;rsquo;re &amp;ldquo;exercise in futility, false hope, and discouragement&amp;rdquo; viewing them as a place of luck where you hate every second of using just hoping you find an out.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
